<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Marv</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_license">License</string>
    <string name="licensed">"This app is licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\") you may not use this app or it's code except in compliance with the License"</string>
    <string name="app_version_name">Marv 1.0 \"Argon\"</string>
    <string name="title_activity_easter_egg">Marv 1.0 Argon</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Go Back</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">MARV\nARGON</string>
    <string name="title_activity_me">About Developer</string>
    <string name="copyright_notice">\n\nMarv 1.0 \"Argon\"\n© Copyright 2016 Siddhant Vinchurkar\nAll rights reserved\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">What can Marv do?</string>
    <string name="info_text">In one line? Marv can do a lot of things; from opening apps to calculating complex math problems - Marv has got it all covered!</string>
    <string name="define_string">You can ask Marv to define words. Suppose you want the definition of the word \'chaos\'. You can say: \"define chaos\"</string>
    <string name="apps_string">Marv can open apps for you. All you have to do is say \"open &lt;app name&gt;\"</string>
    <string name="weather_string">Marv will show you current weather details if you ask \"what\'s the weather like?\" or \"how\'s the weather outside?\"</string>
    <string name="distance_string">Marv checks for obstacles like roadblocks, traffic, road repair work, etc. before telling you the distance between two places and the time it would take you to reach your destination if you happened to leave now. You can ask Marv \"how far is &lt;destination&gt; from &lt;origin&gt;\" to use this feature. Alternatively, you can also say \"what is the distance between &lt;origin&gt; and &lt;destination&gt;\"</string>
    <string name="math_string">Marv is very good at math and can solve complex math problems within seconds. He thinks concepts like differentiation and integration are child\'s play</string>
    <string name="movie_string">Marv can help you decide whether to watch a movie / TV show or not. Just ask \"should I watch &lt;movie / TV show name&gt;\"</string>
    <string name="repeat_string">You can make Marv repeat after you. Just say \"say &lt;whatever you want Marv to say&gt;"</string>
    <string name="emergency_string">The emergency protocol can come in handy in difficult times. It sends a text message to your emergency contact with your location information. To activate the emergency protocol simply say \"activate emergency protocol\" or shout \"help!\"</string>
    <string name="ai_string">Marv uses a very powerful AI engine which is capable of answering many questions in real time. So fire away!</string>
    <string name="translation_string">Marv understands several languages. He can translate words and phrases for you. To use this feature, say \"Translate &lt;word/phrase&gt; to &lt;language&gt;\"</string>
    <string name="alarm_string">Marv can wake you up when you want him to. Say \"wake me up at &lt;time&gt;\" or \"set an alarm for &lt;time&gt;\" to use this feature</string>
    <string name="remind_string">Marv can remind you to do things. Just say \"remind me to &lt;whatever you want Marv to remind you about&gt;\" to use this feature</string>
    <string name="message_string">Marv can read out your messages for you. All you have to do is say \"read my messages\"</string>
    <string name="youtube_string">Marv can search YouTube for you. To use this feature, say \"YouTube\" followed by your search query.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_suggestion">Suggestions?</string>
    <string name="marv">Marv is your personal digital assistant; from opening apps to calculating complex math problems - He has got it all covered!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_marv">About Marv</string>
    <string name="title_welcome_marv">Hi There! I\'m Marv,\nyour Personal Digital Assistant.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_introduction">Introduction</string>
    <string name="desc_intro_slide1">From opening apps to calculating complex math problems - I\'ve got it all covered!</string>
    <string name="title_intro_slide2">Let\'s get you started.</string>
    <string name="desc_intro_slide2">For a seamless experience, make sure that you have granted me all the necessary permissions from the app settings.</string>
    <string name="title_intro_slide3">Tell me a bit about\nyourself.</string>
    <string name="desc_intro_slide3">Your email ID and password are required to sign you in. An account will be created for you automatically if you haven\'t already signed up. Feel free to skip this step.</string>
    <string name="title_intro_slide4">I can do a lot of things.\nThe only limit is your imagination.</string>
    <string name="desc_intro_slide4">But here\'s a few things to begin with:</string>
    <string name="title_intro_slide5">I am still under development.</string>
    <string name="desc_intro_slide5">This is a test version and suggestions are welcome. You can make suggestions or report bugs from my settings.</string>
    <string name="title_intro_slide6">Looks like your device is rooted.</string>
    <string name="desc_intro_slide6">Awesome! I support root access. Enjoy an ad-free version of me just because.</string>

    <!-- API keys/App IDs -->
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-5111839041604013/9274327284</string>
    <string name="interstitial_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-5111839041604013/1751060487</string>
    <string name="youtube_data_api_v3_key">AIzaSyBAs7wpfaCs-j8OQ9N0ZUvDe5e3Ah6xJMw</string>
    <string name="wolfram_alpha_appid">HV857T-5GKYWQQ6HU</string>
    <string name="google_maps_distance_matrix_api_key">AIzaSyDtHpO7JxqY_QXApLnCtRnvJhH_nTRwPLc</string>
    <string name="yandex_translate_api_key">trnsl.1.1.20160313T114655Z.f52b94c074221a90.4a35915a7e41a7b362bd9f7b6497c9ec9209b099</string>
    <string name="shodan_api_key">L4WcmB2MGvatYVI794NYf3xCawQqfwum</string>
    <string name="openweathermap_appid">68ea3692e0f6a70bc937f6de759ba599</string>
</resources>
